A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5 FA1403
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Culture, 1964-2006; 13; 15.19 Cubic Feet 40 letter document boxes
  - Indonesia, 13.7
    - Kelola, Yayasan, Administrative Expenses, 615-00-21148-203.4, 2001 (Box 625, Folder 6)
    - Woekirasari, 525-00-97114-203.4, 1997 (Box 625, Folder 7)
    - Asia Society, 100-00-25039-203.1, 2005 (Box 625, Folder 8)
    - Grauer, Rhoda, 561-00-98032-203.4, 525-00-97112-203.4, 479-00-96118-203.1, 494-00-96119-203.1, 1996-1998 (Box 626, Folder 1-3)
    - Kelola, Yayasan, 615-00-24129-203.3, 2004 (Box 626, Folder 4)
    - Kelola Foundation, 615-00-26145-203.4, 2006 (Box 626, Folder 5)
    - Kelola, Yayasan, 615-00-23040-203.4, 2003 (Box 626, Folder 6)
  - Japan, 13.8
    - Teachers College Columbia University, General Culture-Japan, Other than Correspondence, DF-6632, 1966 (Box 626, Folder 7)
    - Japan Society, Catile, Rand, For: Japan House Exhibition Program, EC-7128, 1971 (Box 627, Folder 1)
    - Japan Society Travel Award, B-6419, 1964 (Box 627, Folder 2)
    - Teachers College, Columbia University, DF-6632, 1966 (Box 627, Folder 3)
    - WGBH Educational Foundation, Boston, TV Project with Nam June Paik, B-70109, 1970 (Box 627, Folder 4)
    - Pollack, Steve (Box 627, Folder 5)
    - Yomota, Goki, B-86107(30)R, 1986 (Box 627, Folder 6)
    - International House of Japan, EC-8233, 1982 (Box 627, Folder 7)
    - Sachiko Yoshihara and Group, EC-8610(30)R, 1986 (Box 627, Folder 8)
    - Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, B-8639(30)R, 1986 (Box 628, Folder 1)
    - Burstein, B-8872(30)R, 1988 (Box 628, Folder 2)
    - Durland, Steven, B-8874(30)R, 1988 (Box 628, Folder 3)
    - Kuryluk, Ewa, B-9154(30), 1991 (Box 628, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts Council on the Arts and Humanities, B-8876(30)R, 1988 (Box 628, Folder 5)
    - International House of Japan, DD-8810(167)R, 1988 (Box 628, Folder 6)
    - Kirchner, Mary Elizabeth, B-9279(30), 1992 (Box 628, Folder 7)
    - Miura, Masashi, JUSAP, B-8463(30)R, 1984 (Box 629, Folder 1)
    - NY International Festival of the Arts, DF-93112, 1993 (Box 629, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Henry, B-8875(30)R, 1988 (Box 629, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Center for the Arts, 488-00-96086-203.1, 1996 (Box 629, Folder 4)
    - Fitch, Douglas, B-9385(30), 1993 (Box 629, Folder 5)
    - Furuhashu, Teiji, B-9373(30), 1993 (Box 630, Folder 1)
    - International House of Japan, 462-00940002-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 630, Folder 2)
    - Jiyu Gakuen, 660-00-22144-203.4, 2002 (Box 630, Folder 3)
    - Lerman, Richard, B-8972(30), 1989 (Box 630, Folder 4)
    - Minegishi, Yuki, B-8758(30)R, 1987 (Box 630, Folder 5)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 100-00-98024-203.3, 1998 (Box 631, Folder 1)
    - Yomota, Goki, B-86107(30)R, 1986 (Box 631, Folder 2-3)
    - Yoneya, Naoko, 704-00-94074-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 631, Folder 4)
    - Hershkovitz, M. and H. Raphael, 704-00-21109-203.1, 2001 (Box 632, Folder 1)
    - Kaldewey, Gunnar, 704-00-23079-203.1, 2003 (Box 632, Folder 2)
    - Temin, Christine, 100-00-25149-203.3, 2005 (Box 632, Folder 3)
  - Korea, 13.9
    - Seoul National University, College of Fine Arts- College of Music, B-7158, 1971 (Box 632, Folder 4)
    - Pio, Elaine, 100-00-20001-203.3 (Box 632, Folder 5)
    - Seoul Institute of the Arts, 100-00-20064-203.1, 2000 (Box 632, Folder 6)
  - Laos, 13.10
    - Bernard-Johnston, Jean, 707-00-94032-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 632, Folder 7)
  - Mongolia, 13.11
    - Mongolian-American Cultural Association, Inc., 100-00-99138-203.1, 1999 (Box 636, Folder 4)
    - Mongolian-American Cultural Association, Inc., 702-00-21028-203.2, 2001 (Box 636, Folder 5)
    - Western Folklife Center, 702-00-23055-203.1, 2003 (Box 636, Folder 6)
  - Nepal, 13.12
    - Arts of Nepal, Distribution, B-7538-AIP, 1975 (Box 636, Folder 7)
    - Bhattarai, Harihar P., B-8694(26)R, 1986 (Box 636, Folder 8)
  - Pakistan, 13.13
    - Faiz Ahmed Faiz, DF-7938, 1979 (Box 637, Folder 1)
  - Philippines, 13.14
    - Benesa, Leonudas V., B-7255, 1972 (Box 637, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Centre Philippines Library, Alej G. Hufana, B-7258-AIP, 1972 (Box 637, Folder 3)
    - Hufana, Alej G., Columbia University, B-6877, DF-7025, DF-7074, 1968-1970 (Box 637, Folder 4)
    - Madarand, Mariano N., B-6944, 1969 (Box 637, Folder 5)
    - Manuud, Antonio P. G., DF-6842, DF-6914, 1968-1969 (Box 638, Folder 1)
    - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation, Abreu, Belen H., B-7361, 1973 (Box 638, Folder 2)
    - General Culture-Philippines, Roces, Alejandro R., DF-8444, 1984 (Box 638, Folder 3)
    - Global Indigenous Cultural Olympics, 100-00-96005-203.000-3, 1996 (Box 638, Folder 4)
    - Smithsonian Institution, Cultural Center of Philippines, 494-00-96043-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 638, Folder 5)
    - Roces, Marian Pastor, 655-00-24100-203.1, 2004 (Box 638, Folder 6)
  - Sikkim, 13.15
    Sikkim (India)
    - Bank Street College of Education, DF-6894, 1968 (Box 638, Folder 7)
    - Denjongpa, Sonam Paljor, DF-72120, B-7324, B-7428, DF-73107, B-7528, 1972-1974 (Box 638, Folder 8)
  - Singapore, 13.16
    - Tan, Beng Luan, B-9026, 1990 (Box 639, Folder 1)
    - The Kitchen, Ong Keng Sen Travel, 100-00-24027-203.3, 2004 (Box 639, Folder 2)
  - Sri Lanka, 13.17
    - Goonetileke, H. A. Ian, B-7343, 1973 (Box 639, Folder 3)
  - Thailand, 13.18
    - Arts Council of Thailand, Bhirasri Art Centre, B-6513-1, 1965 (Box 639, Folder 4)
    - Piradej, Pira P., Bhirasri Art Centre, B-6513-2, DF7186, 1965-1971 (Box 639, Folder 5)
    - Arts Council of Thailand, B-6513, 1965 (Box 639, Folder 6)
    - Jumsai, Met Ting, B-7848-AIP, 1978 (Box 639, Folder 7)
    - Saeng Arun Arts Centre, 100-00-96004-203.000-3, 1996 (Box 640, Folder 1)
    - Tansukanun, Pranom, 100-00-95107-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 640, Folder 2)
    - Kitamit, 100-00-22031-203.3, 2002 (Box 640, Folder 3)
  - Tibet, 13.19
    - Dorjee, Nima, B-74104, 1974 (Box 640, Folder 4)
    - Losang, Khyongla, B-7227, 1972 (Box 640, Folder 5)
    - Tibetan Foundation, EC-7597, 1975 (Box 640, Folder 6)
    - Tibetan Foundation, Tibetan Music, Dance and Drama Society, EC-7597, 1975 (Box 640, Folder 7)
    - Tibetan Foundation, Library of Tibetan Works and Archives, Thanka Painting Project, EC-7597, 1975 (Box 640, Folder 8)
    - Tibetan FD, Library of Tibetan Works and Archives, EC-7597, DF-7784, B-7848-AIP, 1975-1978 (Box 640, Folder 9)
    - Tibetan Music, Dance and Drama Society, Samdup, Thubten, DF-7752, 1977 (Box 641, Folder 1)
    - Tibet Fund, DF-8450, 1984 (Box 641, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam, 13.20
    - Indiana University, Thinh and Thanh, 702-00-97065-203-1, 1970 (Box 641, Folder 3)
    - Phillips, Herbert, B-9334(314), 1999 (Box 641, Folder 4)
    - Indochina Arts Project, 703-00-95098-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 641, Folder 5)
    - Indochina Arts Project, B-9390 (27), 1993 (Box 641, Folder 6)
    - Institute for Folklore Studies, 706-00-99077-203.1, 1999 (Box 641, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam Institute of Musicology, Folk Dance, and Choreography, 100-00-95035-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 642, Folder 1)
- Literature, 1964-2004; 14; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Asia, 14.1
    - P.E.N. American Center, B-6669 (Box 642, Folder 1)
    - State University of Iowa Foundation, Other than Correspondence, B-6411, B-6624, 1964-1966 (Box 642, Folder 2)
    - State University of Iowa Foundation, B-6411, B-6624, 1964-1966 (Box 642, Folder 3)
    - Compton, Boyd, DF-7555, 1975 (Box 642, Folder 4)
    - P.E.N. American Center, B-6669, 1966 (Box 642, Folder 5)
  - Indonesia, 14.2
    - Sastrowardojo, Subagio, B-6658, EC-7022, DF-6601, DF-6643, DF-7094, DF-70117, 1966-1970 (Box 642, Folder 6)
  - Japan, 14.3
    - Committee for International Poetry, EC-8549(30)R, 1985 (Box 642, Folder 7)
    - Academy of American Poets, B-6960, 1969 (Box 643, Folder 1)
    - Thornton, Sybil, EC-8550(30)R, 1985 (Box 643, Folder 2)
    - Ryo, Michiko, B-9274(30), 1992 (Box 643, Folder 3)
    - Charlip, Remy, 704-00-22100-203.1, 2002 (Box 643, Folder 4)
    - Orenstein, Peggy, 704-00-20100-203.1, 2000 (Box 643, Folder 5)
    - Ishii, Tatsuhiko, 704-00-97086-203.000-1, 500-00-97087-203.000-1, 100-00-99128.3, 1997 (Box 643, Folder 6)
    - Tanaka, Shimon (Box 643, Folder 7)
    - Moore, Susanna, 704-00-98085-203.1, 1998 (Box 644, Folder 1)
    - Morris, Tracie, 704-00-97096-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 644, Folder 2)
    - Suiter, John, 704-00-24084-203.1, 2004 (Box 644, Folder 3)
  - Korea, 14.4
    - Ko, Won, DF-6747, 1967 (Box 644, Folder 4)
- Museology, 1962-2006; 15; 23.55 Cubic Feet 62 letter document boxes
  - Asia, 15.1
    - UNESCO-ICOM, B-6729, B-6880, B-7055, B-7157, 1967-1971 (Box 644, Folder 5)
    - ICOM Conference (8th General Conference, Cologne-Munich) (Box 644, Folder 6)
    - ICOM-Regional Agency in Asia, Monreal, DF-7669, DF-7875, DF-7888, 1976-1978 (Box 645, Folder 1)
    - Chase, William Thomas, Freer Gallery of Art, DF-7239, 1972 (Box 645, Folder 2)
    - M. H. de Young Memorial Museum, Brundage Symposium, B-6685, 1966 (Box 645, Folder 3)
    - Chase, William Thomas, Other than Correspondence and Duplications, DF-7239, 1972 (Box 645, Folder 4)
    - Dudley, Dorothy, B-7048, 1970 (Box 645, Folder 5)
    - Honolulu Academy of Arts, B-6628, 1966 (Box 646, Folder 1-2)
    - Honolulu Academy of Arts, B-6628, DF-7092, 1966 (Box 646, Folder 3)
    - Hohnson, Benjamin, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, B-7304, 1973 (Box 646, Folder 4)
    - ICOM-UNESCO, Publication "Museum", Lehmbruck, M., B-7261, 1972 (Box 646, Folder 5)
    - Museum of Modern Art, Karpel, Bernard, B-6621, 1966 (Box 646, Folder 6)
    - Morley, Grace, B-6977, DF-70118, 1969-1970 (Box 647, Folder 1)
    - Tintori, Leonetto, B-6515, 1965 (Box 647, Folder 2)
    - International Centre for Study of Preservation and Restoration of Cultural Property, B-6824, B-6950, DF-7080, B-7063, 1968-1970 (Box 647, Folder 3)
    - International Centre for Conservation, Thakor, Mistaea and Naktong, DF-7553, DF-7663, 1975-1976 (Box 647, Folder 4)
    - International Centre for Restoration and Preservation of Cultural Property, B-7402, 1971-1974 (Box 647, Folder 5)
    - ICOM Regional Agency in Asia, Grace Morely, DF-7669, DF7875, DF-7888, B-7935, B-8025, 1978 June (Box 648, Folder 1)
    - Honolulu Academy of Arts, Other than Correspondence, B-6539, B-6628, 1965-1966 (Box 648, Folder 2)
    - Museology-Asia, Adams, Celeste, B-8845(55)R, 1988 (Box 648, Folder 3)
    - Museology-Asia, Otsuka, Ronald, B-8737(55)R, 1987 (Box 648, Folder 4)
    - Museology-Asia, Swinton, Elizabeth, B-86108(55)R, 1986 (Box 648, Folder 5)
    - Kuwayama, George, B-9097(314), 1990 (Box 649, Folder 1)
    - Leoshko, Janice, B-9098(314), 1990 (Box 649, Folder 2)
    - Farver, Jane, 706-00-94059-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 649, Folder 3)
    - Poster, Amy, B-9168(314), 1991 (Box 649, Folder 4)
    - Altshuler, Bruce, 100-0-22036-203.3, 2002 (Box 649, Folder 5)
    - Desai, Vishaka, B-9182(314), 1991 (Box 649, Folder 6)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, 100-00-20136-203.3, 2000 (Box 651, Folder 2)
    - Fowle, Kate, 706-00-24068-203.1, 2004 (Box 649, Folder 7)
  - Bangladesh, 15.2
    - Dacca Museum Training Program, Mr. Mahmud, Mr. Moshin, Museo-Bangledesh (Box 649, Folder 8)
    - Haque, Enamul, DF-7290, 1972 (Box 650, Folder 1)
    - Dacca Museum Training Program, Conservation-Installation-Administration, Moshin, Mohammed, Muahmed, Firoz, B-7457-MCR, 1974 (Box 650, Folder 2)
    - Dacca Museum, Bangladesh Library, B-7365-MCR, EC-7665-MCR, 1973-1976 (Box 650, Folder 3)
    - Yahia, Mohammed Abu, B-8002, 1980 (Box 650, Folder 4)
    - Haque, Enamul, B-8631(26)R, 1986 (Box 651, Folder 1)
  - Bhutan, 15.3
    Bhutan
    - Peabody Essex Museum, 706-00-20090-203.1, 2000 (Box 651, Folder 3)
    - Namgyel, Dorji, 702-00-25049-203.1, 2005 (Box 651, Folder 4)
  - Cambodia, 15.4
    - Sieu, Eng Keat, Interconcerto, B-7351, 1973 (Box 651, Folder 5)
    - Touch, Hab, 634-00-21158-203.1, 2001 (Box 651, Folder 6)
    - Darith, Ea, 100-00-26126-203.3, 718-00-24105-203.2, 2006 (Box 652, Folder 1)
    - Samen, Khun, 634-00-23024-203.2, 2003 (Box 652, Folder 2)
  - China, 15.5
    - Fu, Shen, Princeton University, B-6882, EC-7019, B-7222, 1968-1972 (Box 652, Folder 3)
    - Ishida, Hou-Mei, B-7780, B-7850, 1977-1978 (Box 652, Folder 4)
    - Wu, Marshall Pei-Sheng, N-7328 (Canceled), 1973 (Box 652, Folder 5)
    - American Association of Museums, DF-8034, 1980 (Box 652, Folder 6)
    - Gittinger, Mattiebelle, B-8738(55)R, 1987 (Box 653, Folder 1)
    - Knight, Michael, EC-88100(55)R, 1988 (Box 653, Folder 2)
    - Lee, Robert, B-8660(55)R, 1986 (Box 653, Folder 3)
    - Oba, Takemitsu, B-8739(55)R, 1987 (Box 653, Folder 4)
    - White, Julia, EC-8888(55)R, 1988 (Box 653, Folder 5)
    - Wu, Marshall, EC-88101(55)R, 1988 (Box 653, Folder 6)
    - Huang, Qixu, B-8926, 1989 (Box 653, Folder 7)
    - Lim, Lucy, B-8661(55)R, 1986 (Box 653, Folder 8)
    - Little, Stephen, B-8847(55)R, 1988 (Box 654, Folder 1)
    - Owyoung, Steven D., B-9053(56), 1990 (Box 654, Folder 2)
    - Ren, Hai, B-8929, 1989 (Box 654, Folder 3)
    - Museology-Asia, Lerner, Martin, 706-00-97060-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 654, Folder 4)
    - Barnes, Laurie Erin, 706-00-95064-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 654, Folder 5)
    - Kamberi, Dolkun, B-9251(26), B-9127(26), B-9023, B-8945(26), 1989-1995 (Box 654, Folder 6-7)
    - So, Jenny Fong-suk, B-9244(314), 1992 (Box 655, Folder 1)
    - Shanghai Museum of History and Art, 703-00-96018-203.000-2, 1996 (Box 655, Folder 2)
    - Yang, Xiaoneng, 706-00-95066-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 655, Folder 3)
    - Chase, W. Thomas, B-8846(55)R, 1988 (Box 655, Folder 4)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, DF-8912, 1989 (Box 655, Folder 5)
    - Freer Gallery of Art, 706-00-94065-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 655, Folder 6)
    - London, Barbara, 706-00-97075-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 655, Folder 7)
    - Xi, Sancai and Decai Cong, 702-00-22017-203.2 (Box 655, Folder 8)
    - Freer Gallery of Art, 706-00-24073-203.1, 2004 (Box 655, Folder 9)
    - Li, Zhongmou, 506-00-97141-203.000.4, 1997 (Box 655, Folder 10)
    - Liu, Feng, 703-00-21124-203.000-1, 2001 (Box 655, Folder 11)
    - Ma, Chengyuan, 705-00-96123-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 656, Folder 1)
    - World Momuments Fund, 702-00-24004-203.2, 2004 (Box 656, Folder 2)
    - Yin, Tongyun, 710-00-21081-203.1, 100-00-20042-203.1, 2000 (Box 656, Folder 3)
    - Zhang, Zhaoui, 703-00-96092-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 656, Folder 4-5)
  - Hong Kong, 15.6
    - Wong, Sarli, B-8932, B-8877(59)R, 1988-1989 (Box 657, Folder 1)
    - Chan, Anna, 452-00-95053-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 657, Folder 2)
    - Wong, Wo Bik, B-9359(HK), 1993 (Box 657, Folder 3)
    - Hong Kong Arts Centre, 100-00-22014-203.2, 2002 (Box 657, Folder 4)
    - Tam, Eve Mei Yee, 751-00-25066-203.1, 2005 (Box 658, Folder 1)
  - India, 15.7
    - Jaipur Msueum Conservation Project, Kajiani-Sonday, B-7453, DF-7536, DF-7516, DF-74109, DF-74110, 1974-1975 (Box 658, Folder 2)
    - Ray, Dilip K., DF-7240, 1972 (Box 658, Folder 3)
    - Dwivedi, V. P., DF-6518, DF-6801, 1965; 1968 (Box 658, Folder 4)
    - Baxi, Smita J., B-6927, 1969 (Box 658, Folder 5)
    - Agrawal, O. P., Travel, International Institute for Conservation Conference, B-70110-MCR, 1970 (Box 658, Folder 6)
    - Ray, Nityananda Das, Victoria Conservation Department, B-6980, 1969 (Box 658, Folder 7)
    - Roy, Sachin, ICOM, DF-6630, 1966 (Box 659, Folder 8)
    - Sahasrabudhe, Orabha, ICOM, DF-6629, 1966 (Box 659, Folder 1)
    - Sajnani, H. N, DF-6845, 1968 (Box 659, Folder 2)
    - Sarkar, Mr. Anal, DF-6542 (Box 659, Folder 3)
    - Satyamurti, S. T., Madras Museum, B-7345-AIP, B-7033, B-7344, DF-7376, DF-7384, B-7258-AIP, 1970-1973 (Box 659, Folder 4)
    - Sharotri, G., DF-6550, 1965 (Box 659, Folder 5)
    - Shetti, Chalchandra V., NYU, B-7209, EC-7131, 1971-1972 (Box 659, Folder 6)
    - Singh, (Mrs.) C., University of Michigan, B-6768, 1967 (Box 659, Folder 7)
    - Talwar, M. S., DF-6674, 1966 (Box 659, Folder 8)
    - UNESCO, Technical Assistance Board, DF-6637, DF-6638, DF-6639, DF-6675, 1966 (Box 659, Folder 9)
    - Vijayarachavan, K. R., DF-6250, DF-6973, DF-6975, DF-6995, 1962-1969 (Box 659, Folder 10)
    - Gairola, T. R., Interconcerto, DF-6521, DF-6645, ICOM Conference, B-6627, 1965-1966 (Box 659, Folder 11)
    - Gandhi, M. R., B-7030, DF-7180, 1970-1971 (Box 660, Folder 1)
    - Garga, Pre, Prakash, B-6653, 1966 (Box 660, Folder 2)
    - Gorakshkar, S. V., B-6716, DF-6787, 1967 (Box 660, Folder 3)
    - Gupte, Padmakar G., B-7337, 1973 (Box 660, Folder 4)
    - Hendy, Philip, B-6728, 1967 (Box 660, Folder 5)
    - ICOM Conference, General B-6627, 1966 (Box 660, Folder 6)
    - ICOM Conference, Moti Chandra, B-6627, 1966 (Box 660, Folder 7)
    - ICOM Conference, Abdul Waheed Khan, B-6627, 1966 (Box 660, Folder 8)
    - ICOM Conference, Ajit Mookerjee, B-6627, 1966 (Box 661, Folder 1)
    - ICOM Conference, Anand Kishna, B-6627, 1966 (Box 661, Folder 2)
    - ICOM Conference, C. Sivaramamurti, B-6627, 1966 (Box 661, Folder 3)
    - International Center for Restoration and Preservation of Cultural Property, DF-6705, 1967 (Box 661, Folder 4)
    - Kala, S. C., B-6928, 1969 (Box 661, Folder 5)
    - Krishna, Kalyan, University of Michigan, EC-7116, B-7207, DF-72117, 1971-1972 (Box 661, Folder 6)
    - Mukhopadhyay, Smair, Institute of International Education (IIE), B-6829, 1968 (Box 661, Folder 7)
    - Nair, S. M., Institute of International Education (IIE), B-6884, 1968 (Box 661, Folder 8)
    - Conservation Laboratory (Brooks), National Museum, O. P. Agrawal, B-7258, DF-71115, 1971-1972 (Box 661, Folder 9)
    - National Museum, New Delhi, DF-6765, 1967 (Box 662, Folder 1)
    - Pal, Pratapaditya, DF-6490, 1964 (Box 662, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, Exhibition by S. Kramrisch, DF-6519, 1965 (Box 662, Folder 3)
    - Janapada Academy, B-7258-AIP, 1972 (Box 662, Folder 4)
    - Andhare, S. K., DF-6549, 1965 (Box 662, Folder 6)
    - Hotchand, Basandani, ICC, EC-7663, 1976 (Box 662, Folder 7)
    - John, K. J., B-7711, 1977 (Box 663, Folder 1)
    - Krishna, Naval, B-7712, B-7809, B-7882, DF-7792, 1977-1978 (Box 663, Folder 2)
    - Sahai, Yaduendra, B-7515, 1975 (Box 663, Folder 3)
    - Sharma, Brijendra Nath, B-7615, 1976 (Box 664, Folder 1)
    - Jaipur Museum Conservation Project, Sonday and Kajitan, Project Related Materials, B-7453, 1974 (Box 664, Folder 2)
    - Rao, M. S. Nagaraja, Institute of Fine Arts, NYU, EC-7006, DF-7073, 1970 (Box 664, Folder 3)
    - ICOM Conference, Bedekar, Vasnat Hari, B-6627, B-7243, DF-8064 (Travel), DF-72116 (Travel), 1966-1980 (Box 665, Folder 1)
    - Jain, Joytrinda, B-8006, 1980 (Box 665, Folder 2)
    - Museology-India, Kajitani, Nobuko, DF-88109, 1988 (Box 665, Folder 3)
    - Andhare, Shridhar, DF-9093, 1990 (Box 665, Folder 4)
    - Desai, Kalpana, B-9034(26), 1990 (Box 665, Folder 5)
    - Gorakshakr, Sadashiv, DF-8061, 1980 (Box 666, Folder 1)
    - John, K. T., B-7808, 1978 (Box 666, Folder 2)
    - Kharbanda, Gulshan, DF-8031, 1980 (Box 666, Folder 3)
    - Nair, S. M., DF-8405, 1984 (Box 666, Folder 4)
    - Ranjit, Vasavan Prema, B-8633(26)R, DF-8885, B-8693(26)R, 1986-1988 (Box 666, Folder 5)
    - Shihare, Laxmi, ICOM Conference, NYC, 1974 April 8-17, EC-7482, DF-7488 (Box 667, Folder 1)
    - Joshi, Nilkanth Prabhakar, B-8438(26)R, 1984 (Box 667, Folder 2)
    - Chakravarty, K.K., 100-00-96105-203.000-3, 1996 (Box 667, Folder 3)
    - Jain, Joytrindra, B-8006, DF-8668, DF-8918, 1980-1989 (Box 667, Folder 4)
    - Singh, Mahendra, 100-00-97029-203.3, 1997 (Box 667, Folder 5)
    - Jasol, Karni Singh, 702-00-23048-203.1, 2003 (Box 667, Folder 6)
  - Indonesia, 15.8
    - Asmat Museum of Culture and Progress, B-7273MCR (Box 662, Folder 5)
    - Gunardjo, Bambang, Museo-Indo (Box 667, Folder 7)
    - Gunardjo, Bambang, B-7717, 1977 (Box 668, Folder 1)
    - Music-Indonesia, Yeo, Kuei Pin, B-7815, B7914, B-8013, 1978-1980 (Box 668, Folder 2)
    - Central Museum Conservation Project, Sri A. S. Bisht, Chemicals-Equipment-Indian Bronze Expert, DF-71119, DF-7284, DF-7341, DF-7377, DF-73110, 1971-1973 (Box 668, Folder 3)
    - Central Museum, Museum Pusat, Book Contribution, B-7258-AIP, 1972 (Box 668, Folder 4)
    - Central Museum, Museum Pusat, Scholarships: Gunawan Budinarjo, B-7167-MCR, 1971 (Box 668, Folder 5)
    - Cenderwasih University, West Irian, Malcolm Walker, B-7463-MCR, 1974 (Box 668, Folder 6)
    - Kuruwaip, Abraham, B-7517, DF-7582, 1975 (Box 669, Folder 1)
    - Prakoso, Mastini H., B-7248, 1972 (Box 669, Folder 2)
    - Sutarga, Amir, ICOM Symposium on Museum Architecture, Mexico, B-6982, 1968 December 8-14 (Box 669, Folder 3)
    - Wright, John Cotton, DF-7557, B-7747-MCR, 1974-1975 (Box 669, Folder 4)
    - ASMAT Museum of Culture and Progress, Museo-Indonesia (Box 669, Folder 5)
    - Hardjonagoro, R. K. T., DF-7940, 1979 (Box 670, Folder 1)
    - ASMAT Museum of Culture and Progress, B-7573MCR, DF-7897, B-8049 MCR, 1975-1980 (Box 670, Folder 2)
    - Boestami, B-8439(26)R, 1984 (Box 670, Folder 3)
    - Sudarnaji, B-8465(27)R, 1984 (Box 670, Folder 4)
    - Museology-Indonesia, Moenir, Darman, DF-88120, 1988 (Box 671, Folder 1)
    - Budiastra, Putu, R-8222(7), 1982 (Box 671, Folder 2)
    - Gluckman, Dlae Carolyn, B-9332(314), 1993 (Box 671, Folder 3)
    - Jessup, Helen, B-8662(55)R, 1986 (Box 671, Folder 4)
    - Yamamoto, Yoshiko, B-9169(314), 1991 (Box 671, Folder 5)
    - Brennan, Nancy, 339-00-94100-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 671, Folder 6)
    - Coffee, Barbara J., IMDP, 339-00-94101-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 671, Folder 7)
    - Firnharber, Natalie, 339-00-96114-203.000-4, 1996 (Box 671, Folder 8)
    - Dhavida, Usria, IMPD-1992, DD-93125(409), 1992-1993 (Box 672, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton, Roy, 706-00-94062-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 672, Folder 2)
    - Jain-Neubauer, Jutta, 504-00-97122-203.4, 1997 (Box 672, Folder 3)
    - Laksito, Oki, 504-00-98025-203.4, 1998 (Box 672, Folder 4)
    - Nusantara Jaya Foundation, 100-00-98130-203.3, 1984-1994 (Box 672, Folder 5)
    - Nusantara Jaya Foundation, 702-00-98013-203.2, 1998 (Box 672, Folder 6)
    - Reynolds, Barrie, 339-00-95114-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 672, Folder 7)
    - Roembiak, Mientje, 702-00-95049-203.000-1, 339-00-95101-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 672, Folder 8)
    - Rose, Carolyn, 504-00-96115-203.000-4, 1996 (Box 673, Folder 1)
    - Satari, Soejatami, 100-00-95022-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 673, Folder 2)
    - Suriman, 504-00-97153-203.4, 1997 (Box 673, Folder 3)
    - Tahir, Mulyati, 504-00-97133-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 673, Folder 4)
    - Utami, Sri, DD-93124(409), 100-00-96028-203.000-3, 1993-1996 (Box 673, Folder 5)
    - Yayasan, Nusantara Jaya, 339-00-96022-203.000-4, 1996 (Box 673, Folder 6)
    - Younger, Erin, 504-00-98029-203.4, 1998 (Box 674, Folder 1)
    - Yunan, T. M., 339-00-94106-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 674, Folder 2)
    - Wolf, Sara, 504-00-96109-203.000-4, 1996 (Box 674, Folder 3)
    - Hutterer, Karl, 504-00-98030-203.4, 1998 (Box 674, Folder 4)
    - Jain, Joytindra, 504-00-97123-203.4, 1997 (Box 674, Folder 5)
    - Arbi, Yunus, 702-00-99056-203.1, 339-00-98132-203.4, 1998-1999 (Box 674, Folder 6)
    - Arbi, Yunus, 603-00-20143-203.4, 702-00-20070-203.1, 2000 (Box 675, Folder 1)
    - Arbi, Yunus, 339-00-95014-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 675, Folder 2)
    - Duha, Nata?alui, 615-00-24005-203.2, 2004 (Box 675, Folder 3)
    - Kreps, Christina, 706-00-26071-203.000-1, 2006 (Box 675, Folder 4)
    - Mugeni, Muhammad, 339-00-95123-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 676, Folder 1)
    - Ponto, Susan, 504-00-21042-203.4, 2001 (Box 676, Folder 2)
    - Pamuji, Suryanto, 504-00-200010-203.4 (Box 676, Folder 3)
    - Rijoly, Frans, 100-00-21001-203.3, 2001 (Box 676, Folder 4)
    - Sagita, Novia, 615-24006-203.2, 2004 (Box 676, Folder 5)
    - Triyanto, Slamet Hadi, 504-00-20146-203.4, 2001 (Box 676, Folder 6)
  - Japan, 15.9
    - Yamamoto, Chikyo, Museo-Japan, B-6934, 1969 (Box 677, Folder 1)
    - Clapp, Anne, Intermuseum Laboratory, DF-6844, 1968 (Box 677, Folder 2)